Narrator: 1
Your lifestyle
Speaker: What do you usually do in the morning?
How do you relax?
What did you do last weekend?
Narrator: 2
Your home
Speaker: What’s your favourite room in your home?
Are you tidy or untidy?
Did you do a lot of housework last week?
Narrator: 3
Your abilities
Speaker: What languages can you speak?
Can you sing or play a musical instrument?
Why are you learning English?
Narrator: 4 Your places
Speaker: What’s your favourite place to spend the weekend?
Where did you go for your last holiday?
Where are you going to go for your next holiday?
Narrator: 5
Your tastes
Speaker: What’s your favourite time of year?
What book are you reading at the moment?
What kind of TV programmes do you like watching?
v>Narrator: 6
Your experiences
Speaker: What films have you seen recently?
What’s the most beautiful place you’ve ever been to?
Have you ever been to Britain or the USA?